phx.co.in 2016-11-07

# Privacy Policy - Phx.co.in

* * *

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted clearly on the website. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. BY VISITING THIS WEBSITE AND REQUESTING INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES THERON, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO US OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

 **Collection of Information  
** We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. The registered members of our website are automatically added to our site announcement mailing list. You as a subscriber of the mailing list have the option to opt out of these mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any of the newsletter sent to you. The unsubscribe process is automatic and immediate. This site uses a tool which collects your requests for pages and passes elements of them to search engines to assist them in indexing this site. We control the configuration of the tool and are responsible for any information sent to the search engines.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
** The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. **We may do so when:**   
**(1)** permitted or required by law; or,   
**(2)** trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or,   
**(3)** investigating fraud which has already taken place.  
The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. Other than this, we have our own network of websites and portals. From time to time, we may send you the relevant information from these websites or portals also. 

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings, as already mentioned above. 

**Ad Serving  
** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

 **Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us for any clarification.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted on this page.
